<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 18:54:50 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Three lessons I learnt from my Prince2 instructor and what he can teach you</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Say what you are about to do, do it, prove you’ve done it.” That’s how David, my project management instructor summarised the methodology, and what better opportunity to apply this than in this article about what I learnt from him. Below what I took from the 5 day course beyond Prince:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;1-always-know-what-to-do-next&#34;&gt;1. Always Know What to do next.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Who hasn’t found themselves against the wall of ill planning be it personally or professionally? David likes to call us university students “professional students” and I’ve found not having an overall project plan for the semester is the main cause of the procrastination that leads most of us to the 4 weeks of stress mayhem before exams. Still too much too soon can be as bad as too little. Very detailed planning for each stage for the course of a whole project is unrealistic and bound to derail. During day 3 of the course I was really eager to get a headstart and asked “What’s tomorrow’s homework?” to be answered with a conclusive “We’ll worry about that tomorrow.” As Prince2 states: Manage by stages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
